Foster Gunnison, Jr. Papers
© 2006 University of Connecticut
- Series II: Institute for Social Ethics Archive, undated, 1956-1999
  - Subseries A: Related to Homophile Movement, 1956-1999
    - Homosexuality, 1978 November - 1979 April (Box 43:, Folder 498)
    - Homosexuality, 1979 May - 1980 June (Box 43:, Folder 499)
    - Homosexuality, 1980 July - 1985 Septmber, 1993 July (Box 43:, Folder 500)
    - Homosexuality, 1985 October - 1994 February (Box 44:, Folder 501)
    - Lesbian and Women Issues, 1964-1972 (Box 44:, Folder 502)
    - Lesbian and Women Issues, 1973-1977 (Box 44:, Folder 503)
    - Lesbian and Women Issues, 1978-1989 (Box 44:, Folder 504)
    - Lesbian and Women Issues, 1970 May - 1982 August (Box 44:, Folder 505)
    - Lesbian and Women Issues, 1982 September - 1989 May (Box 44:, Folder 506)
    - Artifacts
    - Buttons and Pins, undated, 1967-1975 (Box 80-82:, Folder 664-708)
    - Flag, March on Washington, 1993 (Box 82:, Folder 709)
    - Matchbook, Say It Loud, Gay and Proud, undated (Box 82:, Folder 710)
    - Matchbook, Think Straight, Be Gay, undated (Box 82:, Folder 711)
    - Address Plates, Institute for Social Ethics, undated (Box 84)
  - Subseries B: Related to Smokers Rights, undated, 1969-1993
    - Correspondence
    - Allied Organizations for Freedom, 1986 (Box 60:, Folder 760)
    - American Cancer Research Fund, 1985 (Box 60:, Folder 761)
    - American Medical Association, 1986 (Box 60:, Folder 762)
    - Amtrak, 1976 (Box 60:, Folder 763)
    - Andrusik, Dana, 1985 (Box 60:, Folder 764)
    - Blumenthal, Jodi, 1990 (Box 60:, Folder 765)
    - Bradford, Jim, 1992 (Box 60:, Folder 766)
    - BTCA Board of Directors, 1990 (Box 60:, Folder 767)
    - Caldeira, Stephen, 1990-1992 (Box 60:, Folder 768)
    - Californians Against Restrictive Legislation, 1992 (Box 60:, Folder 769)
    - CBS Broadcasting Corporation, 1985 (Box 60:, Folder 770)
    - Cigar Magazine, 1979-1981 (Box 60:, Folder 771)
    - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1976-1978 (Box 60:, Folder 772)
    - Clement, David, 1982 (Box 60:, Folder 773)
    - Committee Insuring Anyone's Right to Smoke, 1976 (Box 60:, Folder 774)
    - Connecticut Magazine, 1989 (Box 60:, Folder 775)
    - Connecticut Mutual Life Insurance, 1985 (Box 60:, Folder 776)
    - Connecticut Smokers' Rights, 1992 (Box 60:, Folder 777)
    - Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1975, 1978 (Box 60:, Folder 778)
    - Derevjanik, Maria, 1988 (Box 60:, Folder 779)
    - Deuval, Ernest, 1992 (Box 60:, Folder 780)
    - Dyer, Dennis, 1985 (Box 60:, Folder 781)
    - Eastern Airlines, 1977 (Box 60:, Folder 782)
    - Correspondence, Encyclopedia of Associations, 1987, 1992 (Box 78:, Folder 943)
    - Federal Election Commission, 1983-1984 (Box 60:, Folder 783)
    - Fortune Magazine, 1988 (Box 60:, Folder 784)
    - Franke, Helen, 1980 (Box 60:, Folder 785)
    - Frisone, Anna, 1993 (Box 60:, Folder 786)
    - Gleason, Ann and Freddie, 1987 (Box 60:, Folder 787)
    - Goodale, David, 1992 (Box 60:, Folder 788)
    - Grady, Fred, 1993 (Box 60:, Folder 789)
    - Graves, Fred, 1977 (Box 60:, Folder 790)
    - Greene, Sue, 1993 (Box 60:, Folder 791)
    - Hacker, Richard, 1988 (Box 60:, Folder 792)
    - Haen, Jennifer, undated (Box 60:, Folder 793)
    - Handman, Stephen, 1988 (Box 60:, Folder 794)
    - Hartford Current, 1977-1989 (Box 60:, Folder 795)
    - Henstenburg, Liz, 1992 (Box 60:, Folder 796)
    - Hickey, Richard, 1986 (Box 60:, Folder 797)
    - Hines, Linwood, 1988 (Box 60:, Folder 798)
    - Huhtanen, Robert, 1988 (Box 60:, Folder 799)
    - Humme, Henry, 1990 (Box 60:, Folder 800)
    - Indiana University, 1985 (Box 60:, Folder 801)
    - Individual Rights Association, 1993 (Box 61:, Folder 802)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1976 (Box 61:, Folder 803)
    - Johnson, Billy, 1989 (Box 61:, Folder 804)
    - Kessel, Rick, 1987 (Box 61:, Folder 805)
    - Klamo, Rachel, undated (Box 61:, Folder 806)
    - Larner, Cindy, undated (Box 70:, Folder 949)
    - Lavoy, Kelli, 1993 (Box 61:, Folder 807)
    - Levy, Mickie, 1985-1986 (Box 61:, Folder 808)
    - Longyear, Walter, 1988 (Box 70:, Folder 950)
    - Loucks, Roger, 1988 (Box 61:, Folder 809)
    - Lubin, Leonard, 1977 (Box 61:, Folder 810)
    - Lucas, J. P., 1987 (Box 61:, Folder 811)
    - Lyon, Cassandra, undated (Box 61:, Folder 812)
    - MacKinnon, Michael, 1987 (Box 61:, Folder 813)
    - Merski, Peg, 1992 (Box 61:, Folder 814)
    - Meyer, Ronald, 1984 (Box 61:, Folder 815)
    - Meyer, Ronald, 1984 (Box 61:, Folder 815)
    - Mihalor, Kris, 1993 (Box 61:, Folder 816)
    - Munford, Dillard, 1977 (Box 61:, Folder 817)
    - New York Times, 1985-1986 (Box 61:, Folder 818)
    - Norton, Melissa, 1988 (Box 61:, Folder 819)
    - O'Neal, Shannon, 1993 (Box 61:, Folder 820)
    - Pennsylvanians Who Smoke, 1989 (Box 61:, Folder 821)
    - People Against Media Stereotyping, undated (Box 61:, Folder 822)
    - Perry, Alfred, 1985-1986 (Box 61:, Folder 823)
    - Perske, Martha, undated, 1991 (Box 61:, Folder 824)
    - Perske, Martha, 1992-1993 (Box 61:, Folder 825)
    - Peters, Jordan, 1972 (Box 61:, Folder 826)
    - Philip Morris, 1978-1990 (Box 61:, Folder 827)
    - R. J. Reynolds Tobacco Co., 1985-1989 (Box 61:, Folder 828)
    - R. J. Reynolds Tobacco Co., 1992 (Box 78:, Folder 944)
    - Rockerfeller, Allison and Peter, 1993 (Box 61:, Folder 829)
    - Skirkin, Natalie, 1986 (Box 61:, Folder 830)
    - Smith, Reuben, 1988 (Box 61:, Folder 831)
    - Smoker's Freedom Society, 1988 (Box 61:, Folder 832)
    - Smoker's Ignorance Cards, 1988 (Box 61:, Folder 833)
    - Smokers' Rights Action Group, undated (Box 61:, Folder 834)
    - Smokers' Rights Alliance, 1988-1992 (Box 62:, Folder 835)
    - Smokers' Rights Organization, 1989 (Box 62:, Folder 836)
    - Smokers' Rights USA, 1992-1993 (Box 62:, Folder 837)
    - Smokers United, 1978 (Box 62:, Folder 838)
    - Snyder, Emmor, 1991 (Box 62:, Folder 839)
    - Southern New England Telephone, 1976 (Box 62:, Folder 840)
    - Spellacy, Bourke, 1987-1988 (Box 62:, Folder 841)
    - Stern, Peter, 1987, 1992 (Box 62:, Folder 842)
    - Studies on Smoking, 1976 (Box 62:, Folder 843)
    - Summit Hotel, 1988 (Box 62:, Folder 844)
    - Susan Davis, Company, 1987 (Box 62:, Folder 845)
    - Teitcher, Norman, 1977 (Box 62:, Folder 846)
    - Thomas, George, 1986-1988 (Box 62:, Folder 847)
    - The Tobacco Institute, 1975-1977, 1989 (Box 62:, Folder 848)
    - Unidentified Correspondents, 1985-1992 (Box 62:, Folder 849)
    - United Smoker's Association of America, 1992-1993 (Box 62:, Folder 850)
    - United States Government, Jimmy Carter, 1978 (Box 62:, Folder 851)
    - United States Government, Robert Cruce, 1990 (Box 62:, Folder 852)
    - United States Government, Christopher Dodd, 1990 (Box 62:, Folder 853)
    - United States Government, Leslie Fowler, 1976 (Box 62:, Folder 854)
    - United States Government, Thomas Goodman, 1977 (Box 62:, Folder 855)
    - United States Government, George Gunther, 1987 (Box 62:, Folder 856)
    - United States Government, Nancy Johnson, 1990 (Box 62:, Folder 857)
    - United States Government, Barbara Kennelly, 1986-1990 (Box 62:, Folder 858)
    - United States Government, Joseph Lieberman, 1990 (Box 62:, Folder 859)
    - United States Government, Diane McCarthy, 1977 (Box 62:, Folder 860)
    - United States Government, Will Mahoney, 1977 (Box 62:, Folder 861)
    - Veanus, Elizabeth, 1989 (Box 62:, Folder 862)
    - Wall Street Journal, 1986-1987 (Box 62:, Folder 863)
    - Warburton, David, 1988-1989 (Box 62:, Folder 864)
    - West, Jeanne, 1976 (Box 62:, Folder 865)
    - WDRC Radio, 1988 (Box 62:, Folder 866)
    - WFBS/TV3, 1986 (Box 62:, Folder 867)
    - Windfeldt, Lisa, 1992 (Box 62:, Folder 868)
    - Administrative Records
    - American Puffer Alliance, Broadsides, 1986-1987 (Box 78:, Folder 948)
    - American Puffer Alliance, Fliers, undated (Box 58:, Folder 743)
    - Articles, undated (Box 58:, Folder 744)
    - Articles, 1969-1973 (Box 58:, Folder 745)
    - Articles, 1975-1986 (Box 58:, Folder 746)
    - Articles, 1989-1993 (Box 58:, Folder 747)
    - Article, "Chapter and Verse: Public Smoking,", 1978 (Box 58:, Folder 748)
    - Article, "Repace and Lowrey's Estimate of Lung Cancer, ", undated (Box 58:, Folder 749)
    - Article, "The Resurgence and Validity of Antismoking Legislation,", 1974 (Box 59:, Folder 750)
    - Article, "State Legislation on Smoking and Health,", 1975 (Box 59:, Folder 751)
    - Article, "Vital Statistics,", 1975 (Box 59:, Folder 752)
    - Booklet, "Environmental Tobacco Smoke,", 1983 (Box 59:, Folder 753)
    - Booklet, "Report of the Council for Tobacco Research,", 1984 (Box 59:, Folder 754)
    - Booklet, "Report of the Council for Tobacco Research,", 1985 (Box 59:, Folder 755)
    - Booklet, "Tobacco and the Brilliant,", undated (Box 59:, Folder 756)
    - Booklet, "Tobacco Reporter's Buyer's Guide,", 1985 (Box 59:, Folder 757)
    - Booklet, "Tobacco Science,", 1991 (Box 59:, Folder 758)
    - Brochures, 1985, 1991 (Box 59:, Folder 759)
    - Bumper Stickers, undated (Box 78:, Folder 942)
    - Institute for Social Ethics, Announcements, 1986-1988 (Box 63:, Folder 869)
    - Institute for Social Ethics, A Smoker's Manifesto, Page Proofs, 1989 (Box 78:, Folder 947)
    - Institute for Social Ethics, Articles by Gunnison, 1992-1993 (Box 63:, Folder 870)
    - Institute for Social Ethics, Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 63:, Folder 871)
    - Institute for Social Ethics, Handwritten Notes, 1987-1988 (Box 63:, Folder 872)
    - Institute for Social Ethics, Handwritten Notes, 1989 (Box 63:, Folder 873)
    - Institute for Social Ethics, Handwritten Notes, 1988 (Box 63:, Folder 874)
    - Institute for Social Ethics, Mock-ups for Handouts, undated (Box 63:, Folder 875)
    - Institute for Social Ethics, Petitions, 1 of 2, 1989 (Box 63:, Folder 876)
    - Institute for Social Ethics, Petitions, 2 of 2, 1989 (Box 63:, Folder 877)
    - Institute for Social Ethics, Position Statement, 1986 (Box 63:, Folder 878)
    - Institute for Social Ethics, Press Release, 1986-1989 (Box 63:, Folder 879)
    - Merchandise Promotion, undated (Box 63:, Folder 880)
    - Merchandise Promotion, 1981-1988 (Box 63:, Folder 881)
    - Merchandise Promotion, 1991-1993 (Box 64:, Folder 882)
    - Newsletter Subscription Forms, 1980-1992 (Box 64:, Folder 883)
    - Smoker's Congress, 1988 (Box 64:, Folder 884)
    - Correspondence, Smoker's Congress, Notepad, 1988 (Box 64:, Folder 885)
    - Smokers Conference, Travel Arrangements, 1988 (Box 64:, Folder 886)
    - Smoker's Congress, Travel Arrangements, 1988 (Box 64:, Folder 887)
    - Tobacco Conference, 1975 (Box 64:, Folder 888)
    - Print Material
    - Action on Smoking and Health, 1978-1992 (Box 64:, Folder 889-891)
    - American Smokers Alliance, 1989-1990 (Box 65:, Folder 892)
    - American Smokers Alliance, Booklet, "The Great American Smoker's Journal,", undated (Box 65:, Folder 893)
    - American Cancer Society, 1980, 1985 (Box 65:, Folder 894-895)
    - American Heart Association, 1986 (Box 65:, Folder 896)
    - American Lung Association, 1976, 1985, 1986 (Box 65:, Folder 897-898)
    - American's for Nonsmokers' Rights, 1990 (Box 65:, Folder 899)
    - American Right to Smoke, 1988 (Box 65:, Folder 900)
    - The American Tobacco Company, 1990 (Box 65:, Folder 901)
    - The Cancer Research Foundation, 1988 (Box 78:, Folder 946)
    - Choice, R. J. Reynold Tobacco, 1988 (Box 65:, Folder 902)
    - Connecticut Smokers' Rights, 1992 (Box 65:, Folder 903)
    - Derfindustries, Smoker's Revenge Kit, undated (Box 65:, Folder 904)
    - Freedom Organization for the Right to Enjoy Smoking Tobacco, 1992 (Box 65:, Folder 905)
    - Group Against Smoking Pollution, 1983 (Box 65:, Folder 906)
    - Growing Resentment Over Anti-Freedom Noises, 1984 (Box 65:, Folder 907)
    - Individual Rights Association, 1993 (Box 65:, Folder 908)
    - Michigan Tobacco and Candy Distributors and Association, undated (Box 65:, Folder 909)
    - National Smokers Association, undated (Box 65:, Folder 910)
    - Philip Morris, News Release, The American Smokers- an economic force, 1988 (Box 65:, Folder 911)
    - Philip Morris, Brochures, 1988 (Box 66:, Folder 912)
    - Philip Morris, Handouts and Articles, 1986-1990 (Box 66:, Folder 913)
    - San Franciscans Against Government Intrusion, 1983 (Box 66:, Folder 914)
    - Smokers' Caucus, 1990 (Box 66:, Folder 915)
    - Smoker's Freedom Society, 1988 (Box 66:, Folder 916)
    - Smokers' Rights, 1988-1992 (Box 66:, Folder 917)
    - Smokers' Rights Action Group, 1991-1992 (Box 66:, Folder 918)
    - Smoker's Rights Alliance, Letters and Newsletters, 1987-1992 (Box 66:, Folder 919)
    - Smoker's Rights Alliance, Bylaws and Ephemera, undated (Box 66:, Folder 920)
    - Smokefree Educational Service, 1992 (Box 66:, Folder 921)
    - Stop Teenage Addiction to Tobacco, 1988-1991 (Box 66:, Folder 922)
    - The Tobacco Institute, Articles, 1971-1984 (Box 67:, Folder 923)
    - The Tobacco Institute, Article, "Smoking and Health,", 1979 (Box 67:, Folder 924)
    - The Tobacco Institute, Article, "The Cigarette Consumer Controversy,", 1979 (Box 67:, Folder 925)
    - The Tobacco Institute, Booklets, 1982-1986 undated (Box 67:, Folder 926-929)
    - The Tobacco Institute, Brochures, undated (Box 68:, Folder 930-934)
    - The Tobacco Institute, Handouts, undated, 1984, 1987, 1990 (Box 68:, Folder 935-936)
    - The Tobacco Institute, Memos with Attached Brochures, 1978-1990 (Box 68:, Folder 937-939)
    - Tobacco Journal International, 1986 (Box 78:, Folder 945)
    - United Smokers Association of America, 1992-1993 (Box 68:, Folder 940)
    - Artifacts
    - Ashtrays, undated (Box 79:)
    - Proud Puffer, 1988 (Box 83:, Folder 941)
    - Business card holder, American Puffer Alliance, undated (Box 83:, Folder 1050)
    - Cigar Cutter, undated (Box 83:, Folder 1051)
- Series III: North American Conference of Homophile Organizations (NACHO), undated, 1966-1970
  - Subseries A: Correspondence, 1967-1970
    - General Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 45:, Folder 507)
    - Foster Gunnison to/from Bob Martin, 1967 January - March (Box 45:, Folder 508)
    - Foster Gunnison to/from Bob Martin, 1967 April - December (Box 45:, Folder 509)
    - Foster Gunnison to/from Bob Martin, 1968 January - March (Box 45:, Folder 510)
    - Foster Gunnison to/from Bob Martin, 1968 April (Box 45:, Folder 511)
    - Foster Gunnison to/from Bob Martin, 1968 May - December (Box 45:, Folder 512)
    - Foster Gunnison to/from Bob Martin, 1969 January - April (Box 45:, Folder 513)
    - Foster Gunnison to/from Bob Martin, 1969 April - May (Box 45:, Folder 514)
    - Foster Gunnison to/from Bob Martin, 1969 May - December (Box 45:, Folder 515)
    - Foster Gunnison to/from Bob Martin, 1970 (Box 45:, Folder 516)
    - to/from Foster Gunnison, 1967 (Box 45:, Folder 517)
    - to/from Foster Gunnison, 1968 Feb-May (Box 46:, Folder 518)
    - to/from Foster Gunnison, 1968 May-Jun (Box 46:, Folder 519)
    - to/from Foster Gunnison, 1968 Jun-Dec (Box 46:, Folder 520)
    - to/from Foster Gunnison, 1969 (Box 46:, Folder 521)
    - to/from Foster Gunnison, 1970 (Box 46:, Folder 522)
    - to/from Marc Jeffers, 1968-1969 (Box 46:, Folder 523)
    - from Jim Kepner (related to Credential Appeal), 1968 (Box 46:, Folder 524)
    - to/from Bob Martin, undated, 1967 (Box 46:, Folder 525)
    - to/from Bob Martin, 1968 January - August (Box 46:, Folder 526)
    - to/from Bob Martin, 1968 August - December (Box 46:, Folder 527)
    - to/from Bob Martin, 1969 January - February (Box 46:, Folder 528)
    - to/from Bob Martin, 1969 March - April (Box 46:, Folder 529)
    - to/from Bob Martin, 1969 April - December (Box 47:, Folder 530)
    - to/from Bob Martin, 1970 (Box 47:, Folder 531)
  - Subseries B: Conferences, 1966-1970
    - 1966
      - Announcements (Box 47:, Folder 532)
      - Articles Relating to Conference (Box 47:, Folder 533)
      - Attendance Records (Box 47:, Folder 534)
      - Handwritten Notes (Box 47:, Folder 535)
      - Minutes Written After the Conference (Box 47:, Folder 536)
      - Proposals and Handouts (Box 47:, Folder 537)
      - Speeches (Box 47:, Folder 538)
    - 1967
      - Agenda, Attendance and Minutes (Box 47:, Folder 539)
      - Amendments (Box 47:, Folder 540)
      - Announcements (Box 47:, Folder 541)
      - Congressman Meetings (Box 47:, Folder 542)
      - Correspondence (Box 47:, Folder 543)
      - Reports Presented at Conference (Box 47:, Folder 544)
    - 1968
      - Agenda and Minutes (Box 48:, Folder 545)
      - Amendments, Proposals, Resolutions and Rules (Box 48:, Folder 546)
      - Articles Related to Conference (Box 48:, Folder 547)
      - Bulletins Sent by Conference Sponsor (Mattachine Midwest) (Box 48:, Folder 548)
      - Correspondence (Box 48:, Folder 549)
      - Handouts (Box 48:, Folder 550)
      - Handwritten Notes (Box 48:, Folder 551)
      - Reports Presented at Conference (Box 48:, Folder 552)
    - 1969
      - Agenda and Nominations (Box 48:, Folder 553)
      - Articles Related to Conference (Box 48:, Folder 554)
      - Budget Requests, History, Proposals, Resolutions, Rules (Box 48:, Folder 555)
      - Program and Minutes (Box 48:, Folder 556)
      - Register (Box 48:, Folder 557)
      - Reports Presented at Conference (Box 48:, Folder 558)
      - 1970
      - Handwritten Notes (Box 48:, Folder 559)
      - Schedule and Membership List (Box 48:, Folder 560)
  - Subseries C: Committees and Offices, 1966-1970
    - Clearing House, Announcements, 1966-1967 (Box 49:, Folder 561)
    - Clearing House, Announcements, Organization Lists and Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 49:, Folder 562)
    - Clearing House, Newsletter, 1966-1967 (Box 49:, Folder 563)
    - Clearing House, Proposals and Organization Lists, 1966-1967 (Box 49:, Folder 564)
    - Committee on Federal Government, Announcements and Reports, 1968-1970 (Box 49:, Folder 565)
    - Committee on New Organizations, Announcements and Guidelines, 1968 (Box 49:, Folder 566)
    - Committee on Unity, Agenda, Announcements, Proposals and Reports, 1969 (Box 49:, Folder 567)
    - Committee on Unity, Announcements, 1967 (Box 49:, Folder 568)
    - Committee on Unity, Announcements, 1968 (Box 49:, Folder 569)
    - Committee on Unity, Proposals, Questionnaires and Rules, 1968 (Box 49:, Folder 570)
    - Committee on Youth, Announcements, Handouts and Reports, 1969 (Box 49:, Folder 571)
    - Executive Committee, Announcements and Agenda, 1968-1970 (Box 49:, Folder 572)
    - Credentials Office, Blank Forms, undated, 1968 (Box 49:, Folder 573)
    - Credentials Office, Blank Forms, Complete Set, 1969 (Box 49:, Folder 574)
    - Credentials Office, Blank Forms, 1969-1970 (Box 49:, Folder 575)
    - Credentials Office, Bulletins, 1969-1970 (Box 49:, Folder 576)
    - Credentials Office, Compilation of Announcements, Reports, 1 of 2, 1967 (Box 50:, Folder 577-578)
    - Credentials Office, Compilation of Announcements, Reports, 1 of 2, 1968 (Box 50:, Folder 579-580)
    - Credentials Office, Completed Applications for Accreditation, 1968 (Box 50:, Folder 581)
    - Credentials Office, Completed Applications for Accreditation, 1969 (Box 50:, Folder 582)
    - Credentials Office, Completed Applications for Voting, 1970 (Box 50:, Folder 583)
    - Credentials Office, Completed General Information Forms, 1968 (Box 50:, Folder 584)
    - Credentials Office, Completed Observer Voting Sheets, 1968 (Box 50:, Folder 585)
    - Credentials Office, Completed Organization Information Forms, 1 of 2, 1967 (Box 51:, Folder 586-587)
    - Credentials Office, Policies, Handwritten Notes, Rosters and Rules, 1968-1970 (Box 51:, Folder 588)
    - Office of Central Addressing, Bulletins, 1970-1971 (Box 51:, Folder 589)
    - Office of the Parliamentarian, Announcements, Rules and Policies, 1969 (Box 51:, Folder 590)
    - Office of the Treasurer, Announcements, 1970 (Box 51:, Folder 591)
    - Office of the Treasurer, Banking Account Records, 1968 (Box 51:, Folder 592)
    - Office of the Treasurer, Bank Statements and Receipts, 1968-1970 (Box 51:, Folder 593)
    - Office of the Treasurer, Bills, 1968-1969 (Box 51:, Folder 594)
    - Office of the Treasurer, Blank Forms, undated (Box 51:, Folder 595)
    - Office of the Treasurer, Blank Message Pad, undated (Box 51:, Folder 596)
    - Office of the Treasurer, Budget Adjustment Records, 1970 (Box 51:, Folder 597)
    - Office of the Treasurer, Budget and Reconciliation Sheets, 1968-1969 (Box 51:, Folder 598)
    - Office of the Treasurer, Budget Requests, 1969 (Box 52:, Folder 599)
    - Office of the Treasurer, Canceled Checks and Checkbook, 1969-1970 (Box 52:, Folder 600)
    - Office of the Treasurer, Cash and Check Receipt Records, 1969-1970 (Box 52:, Folder 601)
    - Office of the Treasurer, Claim Record, 1969 (Box 52:, Folder 602)
    - Office of the Treasurer, Claim Records, 1 of 3, 1970 (Box 52:, Folder 603-605)
    - Office of the Treasurer, Completed Voucher Forms, 1968-1969 (Box 52:, Folder 606)
    - Office of the Treasurer, Consolidated Extender Records, 1970 (Box 53:, Folder 607)
    - Office of the Treasurer, Correspondence with Bank, 1968 (Box 53:, Folder 608)
    - Office of the Treasurer, General Journal, Budget Records, 1970 (Box 53:, Folder 609)
    - Office of the Treasurer, Handwritten Notes, 1968 (Box 53:, Folder 610)
    - Office of the Treasurer, Income/Expense Records and Communication Records, 1968-1969 (Box 53:, Folder 611)
    - Office of the Treasurer, Receipt of Payment Notice, 1969-1970 (Box 53:, Folder 612)
    - Office of the Treasurer, Reports, 1968-1971 (Box 53:, Folder 613)
    - News Booklet and Bumper Sticker, [1969?] (Box 53:, Folder 614)
- Series IV: Eastern Regional Conference of Homophile Organizations (ERCHO) and Eastern Conference of Homophile Organizations (ECHO), 1964-1973
  - Subseries A: Correspondence, 1969
    - Correspondence and Notes, 1969 (Box 53:, Folder 615)
  - Subseries B: Conferences, 1964-1968
    - 1964
      - Proceedings (Box 53:, Folder 616)
      - Proceedings (Box 53:, Folder 617)
      - Programs (Box 54:, Folder 618)
    - 1965
      - Announcements (Box 54:, Folder 619)
      - Handouts and Handwritten Notes (Box 54:, Folder 620)
      - Programs (Box 54:, Folder 621)
      - Schedules (Box 54:, Folder 622)
      - Speeches (Box 54:, Folder 623)
    - 1967
      - Announcements (Box 54:, Folder 624)
      - Handwritten Notes (Box 54:, Folder 625)
      - Reports (Box 54:, Folder 626)
    - 1968
      - Agenda and Resolutions (Box 54:, Folder 627)
      - Minutes (Box 54:, Folder 628)
      - Reports (Box 54:, Folder 629)
  - Subseries C: Administrative Files and Offices, 1968-1971
    - Addresses, 1968 (Box 54:, Folder 630)
    - Announcements, 1968 (Box 54:, Folder 631)
    - Announcements, 1970 (Box 54:, Folder 632)
    - Bank Statements and Cancel Checks, 1969-1970 (Box 54:, Folder 633)
    - Cash Receipts, Consolidated Extenders and Reconciliation Sheets, 1969-1970 (Box 55:, Folder 634)
    - Credentials Committee, 1968 (Box 55:, Folder 635)
    - Financial Records, 1970 (Box 55:, Folder 636)
    - Financial Records, 1971 (Box 55:, Folder 637)
    - Handouts, 1968 (Box 55:, Folder 638)
    - Office of the Treasure, 1968 (Box 55:, Folder 639)
    - Rules Committee, 1967 (Box 55:, Folder 640)
    - Rules Committee, 1968 (Box 55:, Folder 641)
- Series V: Morris Kight Papers, 1969-1973
  - Subseries A: Correspondence, 1969-1973
    - Correspondence to Kight, 1969 April - 1970 June (Box 55:, Folder 642)
    - Correspondence to Kight, 1970 July - September (Box 55:, Folder 643)
    - Correspondence to Kight, 1970 October (Box 55:, Folder 644)
    - Correspondence to Kight, 1970 November - December (Box 55:, Folder 645)
    - Correspondence to Kight, 1971 January - March (Box 55:, Folder 646)